Finding Aid of the American Academy of Allergy, Asthma & Immunology Records, 1923-2015
University of Wisconsin-Milwaukee Libraries, Archives Department
- Records, 1923-2015, UWM Manuscript Collection 139; 257.9 cubic ft. (741 boxes) 40 binders 1 oversize folder 30,895 digital files (79.5 GB) 1 film reel 4 safety film negatives
  - 5. Related Organizations, 1947-2008
    - Food and Drug Administration
      - Over-the-Counter Ruling, 1986 (Box 218, Folder 5)
      - Panel on Allergenic Extracts, 1984 (Box 218, Folder 6)
      - Panel on Allergenic Extracts, 1985-1986 (Box 218, Folder 7)
      - Peak Flow Meters, 1992 (Box 218, Folder 8)
      - Polymerized Ragweed, 1984-1986 (Box 218, Folder 9)
      - Public Advisory Committee, 1986 (Box 218, Folder 10)
      - Pulmonary-Allergy Drugs Advisory Committee, 1983-1989 (Box 218, Folder 11)
      - Remote Practice, 1988 (Box 218, Folder 12)
      - Sulfiting Agents, 1984-1986 (Box 218, Folder 13)
    - Food and Drug Administration/American Academy of Allergy and Immunology Committee on Drugs, Over-the-Counter Statements, 1984-1993 (Box 216, Folder 6)
    - Food and Drug Administration/American Academy of Allergy and Immunology Committee on Drugs, Over-the-Counter Statements, 1994 (Box 216, Folder 7)
    - Forest Laboratories
      - 1981 (Box 218, Folder 14)
      - 1987-1994 (Box 218, Folder 15)
    - Forum for Medical Affairs
      - 1985-1987 (Box 219, Folder 1)
      - 1992-1993 (Box 219, Folder 2)
    - Forum on Drug Development and Regulation, 1986-1987 (Box 219, Folder 3)
    - Foundation for Biomedical Research, 1988-1996 (Box 219, Folder 4-5)
    - Geigy Pharmaceuticals, 1980-1991 (Box 219, Folder 6)
    - Glaxo, 1984-1994 (Box 219, Folder 7)
    - Graduate Medical Education National Advisory Committee
      - 1980-1990 (Box 219, Folder 8-9)
      - Revisited Planning Group, 1985 (Box 377, Folder 4)
    - Greer Laboratories, 1985-1988 (Box 219, Folder 10)
    - Health Care Quality Alliance
      - 1988-1990 (Box 219, Folder 11)
      - 1991-1993 (Box 220, Folder 1-5)
    - Health Industry Manufacturers Association, 1988-1989 (Box 220, Folder 6)
    - Healthscan Products, Inc., 1993 (Box 220, Folder 7)
    - Hollister-Stier, 1985-1989 (Box 220, Folder 8)
    - Iatric Corporation, 1990 (Box 220, Folder 9)
    - Immune Deficiency Foundation
      - 1988, 1990-1995 (Box 220, Folder 10)
      - 1996-2000 (Box 543, Folder 22)
    - Immunotech, 1988 (Box 221, Folder 1)
    - Independent Allergists Political Action Committee, 1988 (Box 221, Folder 2)
    - Independent Clinical Laboratory Association, 1991-1992 (Box 221, Folder 3)
    - Indoor Air Bulletin, 1993-1994 (Box 446, Folder 24)
    - Institute for Advanced Studies in Immunology and Aging, 1993-1995 (Box 221, Folder 4)
    - Institute of Dermatology, 1990 (Box 221, Folder 5)
    - Institute of Medicine, 1988-1990 (Box 221, Folder 6)
    - Interasma, 1991-1992 (Box 221, Folder 7)
    - International Association of Allergology
      - 1951 (Box 260, Folder 2)
      - 1951-1954 (Box 377, Folder 5)
    - International Association of Allergology and Clinical Immunology
      - 1973-1986 (Box 670, Folder 6)
      - 1981-1989, 1997, 1999-2000 (Box 221, Folder 8)
    - International Asthma Council, 1991 (Box 221, Folder 9)
    - International Congresses on Inflammation, 1989 (Box 221, Folder 10)
    - International Food Information Council, 1986-1996 (Box 221, Folder 11-16)
    - International Pharmaceutical Aerosol Consortium, 1992 (Box 221, Folder 17)
    - International Survey on Asthma Management, 1991 (Box 221, Folder 18)
    - International Union of Immunological Societies, 1981-1993 (Box 222, Folder 1-2)
    - Israeli Society for Allergy and Clinical Immunology, Workshop on Mould Allergy in Children, 1998 (Box 495, Folder 2)
    - Janssen Pharmaceuticals, 1989-1993 (Box 222, Folder 3)
    - Joint Commission on Accreditation of Healthcare Organizations, 1985-1987 (Box 222, Folder 4-5)
    - Joint Council of Allergy and Immunology
      - 1988-1989 (Box 377, Folder 6)
      - 1990 (Box 222, Folder 6-8)
      - 1991-1992 (Box 223, Folder 1-6)
      - 1992 (Box 224, Folder 1)
      - Asthma Care Trust Study, 1984-1986 (Box 224, Folder 2)
      - Correspondence, 1986-1988 (Box 224, Folder 3-6)
      - Newsletter, 1977-1987 (Box 224, Folder 7)
      - Outcome Studies, 1993-1994 (Box 224, Folder 8)
      - Position Statement, Responsibilities of Physicians who Manage Asthma, 1977 (Box 446, Folder 25)
      - Practice Patterns Committee, 1987 (Box 224, Folder 9)
      - Special Committee, 1991 (Box 377, Folder 7)
    - Joint Council of Allergy, Asthma and Immunology
      - Board of Directors' Meeting Agenda Book, 2004 (Box 534, Folder 7)
      - Correspondence, 1998-1999 (Box 675, Folder 7)
      - Medicare Compliance Program Guidelines for Allergy, Asthma, and Immunology, 1999 (Box 520, Folder 40)
      - Mission Statement/Strategic Plan, 1996 (Box 534, Folder 26)
      - Mission and Goals Statement, etc. 1996-1998 (Box 675, Folder 8)
    - Joint Council of Socio-Economics of Allergy, 1974-1977 (Box 446, Folder 26)
    - Joint Legislative Committee, Proposal, 1985 (Box 224, Folder 10)
    - Joint Position Statements, 1985 (Box 224, Folder 11)
    - Joint Task Force on Practice Parameters
      - Practice Parameter on the Diagnosis and Management of Sinusitis, 1998 (Box 520, Folder 39)
      - Practice Parameter on the Management of Rhinitis, Final Draft, 1998 (Box 517, Folder 28)
      - Practice Parameters: Allergy, Asthma and Immunology, 1998 (Box 543, Folder 16-17)
    - Kabi Pharmacia, 1993 (Box 224, Folder 12)
    - Key Pharmaceuticals, 1982-1986 (Box 224, Folder 13)
    - Kimberly-Clark, 1988-1996 (Box 224, Folder 14)
    - Kraft General Foods, 1992 (Box 224, Folder 15)
    - Latin American Congress of Allergy and Immunology, 1989-1993 (Box 225, Folder 1)
    - Lederle Laboratories, 1985 (Box 225, Folder 2)
    - Eli Lilly and Company, 1986-1987 (Box 225, Folder 3)
    - Eli Lilly Grant, 1952 (Box 446, Folder 23)
    - Marcelle Cosmetics, Establishment of Marcelle Research Fund, Correspondence, 1944-1949 (Box 446, Folder 27)
    - Massachusetts Allergy Society, 1989-1992 (Box 225, Folder 4)
    - Mast Immunosystems, 1985-1989 (Box 225, Folder 5)
    - McGraw-Hill, 1991 (Box 225, Folder 6)
    - Medical Exhibitors Association, 1950-1958 (Box 377, Folder 8)
    - Medicard, 1987-1988 (Box 225, Folder 7)
    - Medico, 1985-1989 (Box 225, Folder 8)
    - Merck and Company, 1985, 1999-2000 (Box 225, Folder 9)
    - Merck, Sharp and Dohme Grants, Correspondence, 1959-1963 (Box 446, Folder 28)
    - Merrell-Dow, 1984-1995 (Box 225, Folder 10)
    - Merrell-Dow AAAI Scholarship in Allergy Award, undated (Box 446, Folder 29)
    - Miles Laboratories, 1984-1995 (Box 225, Folder 11)
    - Milwaukee Guidelines for Latex Allergy Precautions, 1991 (Box 225, Folder 12)
    - Mosby Yearbook, 1991-1995 (Box 225, Folder 13-15)
    - Mothers of Asthmatics, 1985-1990 (Box 226, Folder 1-2)
    - Mothers of Asthmatics/Allergy and Asthma Network, Best of the MA Report, undated (Box 446, Folder 30)
    - Muro Pharmaceuticals, 1986-1994 (Box 226, Folder 3)
    - National Academy of Sciences, 1988-1994 (Box 226, Folder 4-5)
    - National Advisory Allergy and Infectious Diseases Council, 1986-1991 (Box 226, Folder 6)
    - National AIDS Information Clearinghouse, 1988 (Box 226, Folder 7)
    - National AIDS Information and Education Program, Booklet, 1990 (Box 446, Folder 31)
    - National Allergy and Asthma Network, 1993 (Box 226, Folder 8-10)
    - National Ambulatory Medical Care Survey, 1991-1993 (Box 227, Folder 1)
    - National Association for Biomedical Research, 1987-1996 (Box 227, Folder 2-3)
    - National Association of Advisors for the Health Professions, 1989 (Box 227, Folder 4)
    - National Association of Health Care Consultants, 1995 (Box 227, Folder 5)
    - National Association of Managed Care Physicians, 1994 (Box 227, Folder 6)
    - National Association of Physicians for the Environment, 1993 (Box 227, Folder 7)
    - National Asthma Education Program, Managing Asthma: A Guide for Schools, 1991 (Box 446, Folder 34)
    - National Asthma Education and Prevention Program, 1993 (Box 227, Folder 8)
    - National Black Nurses Association, 1990 (Box 227, Folder 9)
    - National Board of Medical Examiners, 1990 (Box 227, Folder 10)
    - National Center for Health Education, 1987 (Box 227, Folder 11)
    - National Center for Health Services Research, 1988-1989 (Box 227, Folder 12)
    - National Coalition on Immune System Disorders, 1985-1989 (Box 227, Folder 13)
    - National Committee for Clinical Laboratory Standards
      - 1986-1990 (Box 227, Folder 14-16)
      - 1991-1996 (Box 228, Folder 1)
    - National Council Against Health Fraud, 1988 (Box 228, Folder 2)
    - National Council on Patient Information and Education, 1992-1995 (Box 228, Folder 3)
    - National Health and Nutrition Examination Survey, 1986-1987 (Box 228, Folder 4)
    - National Health Information Center, 1988 (Box 228, Folder 5)
    - National Heart, Lung, and Blood Institute
      - 1984-1993 (Box 228, Folder 6-11)
      - 1993 (Box 229, Folder 1-2)
      - National Asthma Education Program,Guidelines for the Diagnosis and Management of Asthma
        - Executive Summary, 1991 (Box 385, Folder 4)
        - Expert Panel Report, 1991 (Box 229, Folder 3)
      - Slides, 1991, Slides (35 mm) (Box 260, Folder 3)
    - National Institute of Allergy and Infectious Diseases
      - 1989 (Box 260, Folder 4)
      - 1990, 1992 (Box 229, Folder 4-7)
      - 1992-1993 (Box 260, Folder 6-7)
      - 1994 (Box 229, Folder 8)
      - 1994-1996 (Box 230, Folder 1-2)
      - Correspondence
        - 1982-1986 (Box 230, Folder 4-5)
        - 1987 (Box 260, Folder 8)
        - 1988-1989 (Box 230, Folder 6-8)
        - 1989 (Box 231, Folder 1)
      - Task Force Report
        - Asthma and the Other Allergic Diseases, 1979 (Box 260, Folder 9)
        - Asthma and the Other Allergic Diseases, 1979 (Box 261, Folder 1-2)
    - National Institute of Allergy and Infectious Diseases/American Academy of Allergy and Immunology Grants (Box 230, Folder 3)
    - National Institute of Allergy and Infectious Diseases/National Heart, Lung, and Blood Institute Liaison Committee, 1992 (Box 231, Folder 2)
    - National Institute of Allergy and Infectious Diseases Task Force on Immunology and Allergy, Report, 1991 (Box 446, Folder 35)
    - National Institutes of Health
      - 1979-1996 (Box 231, Folder 3-8)
      - Allied Health Committee, Roster, 1988-1994 (Box 428, Folder 12)
      - Bronchoalveolar Lavage Guidelines Committee, 1983 (Box 231, Folder 9)
      - Excerpts from Classics in Allergy, 1988 (Box 231, Folder 10)
      - Food and Drug Administration Liaison Committee, undated (Box 231, Folder 11)
      - Guidelines for the Diagnosis and Management of Asthma, 1997 (Box 377, Folder 9)
      - National Asthma Education and Prevention Program
        - Asthma and Physical Activity in the School, 1995 (Box 446, Folder 36)
        - Asthma Awareness, Curriculum for the Elementary Classroom, 1993 (Box 446, Folder 37)
        - Asthma Management in Minority Children, 1995 (Box 446, Folder 38)
        - Considerations for Diagnosing and Managing Asthma in the Elderly, 1996 (Box 446, Folder 39)
      - Nurses: Partners in Asthma Care, 1995 (Box 377, Folder 10)
    - National Library of Medicine, 1988-1990 (Box 231, Folder 12)
    - National Medical Association, 1985-1995 (Box 231, Folder 13)
    - National Medical Specialty Society, 1979-1990 (Box 231, Folder 14)
    - National Museum of Health and Medicine Foundation, 1990-1992 (Box 232, Folder 1)
    - National Research Council
      - 1980-1991 (Box 232, Folder 2)
      - Multiple Chemical Sensitivities, 1992 (Box 446, Folder 40)
    - National Resident Matching Program, 1981-1987 (Box 232, Folder 3)
    - National Restaurant Association, 1992 (Box 232, Folder 4)
    - National Society for Medical Research, 1978-1992 (Box 232, Folder 5-6)
    - New England Society of Allergy
      - 1986-1987 (Box 232, Folder 7)
      - Correspondence, 1991-1992 (Box 455, Folder 24)
    - NMS Pharmaceuticals, 1987 (Box 232, Folder 8)
    - Nonprescription Drug Manufacturers Association, 1989 (Box 232, Folder 9)
    - Norwich Eaton Pharmaceuticals, 1985-1990 (Box 232, Folder 10)
    - Nutrasweet Company, 1985-1989 (Box 232, Folder 11)
    - Occupational Safety and Health Administration, 1990-1991 (Box 232, Folder 12)
    - Office of Technology Assessment, 1987-1991 (Box 232, Folder 13)
    - OUM Group, 1988 (Box 232, Folder 14)
    - Pan American Allergy Society, 1986-1987 (Box 232, Folder 15)
    - Parke-Davis, 1984-1990 (Box 232, Folder 16)
    - Patient Access Coalition, undated (Box 534, Folder 28)
    - Pennsylvania Allergy Association, Annual Meeting, 1991 (Box 455, Folder 25)
    - People to People International, 1981-1987 (Box 232, Folder 17)
    - Pfizer, Executive Directors Forum, 1984-1993 (Box 232, Folder 18)
    - Pharmaceutical Manufacturers Association
      - 1986 (Box 232, Folder 19)
      - 1987-1988 (Box 233, Folder 1-6)
      - 1988-1991 (Box 261, Folder 3-6)
      - 1992-1994 (Box 234, Folder 1-4)
    - Pharmaceutical Research and Manufacturers of America, 1994-1995 (Box 234, Folder 5)
    - Pharmacia Allergy Research Foundation, 1987-1992 (Box 234, Folder 6)
    - Pharmacia Diagnostics
      - 1984 (Box 234, Folder 7)
      - 1985-1988 (Box 235, Folder 1)
    - Physician Drug Dispensing Legislation, 1987 (Box 235, Folder 2)
    - Physician Payment Review Commission, 1987-1993 (Box 235, Folder 3)
    - Pourquoi Pas, 1988 (Box 235, Folder 4)
    - Practice Parameter Survey (JCAAI), December 1999 (Box 675, Folder 9)
    - Practicing Physician Advisory Council, 1994 (Box 235, Folder 5)
    - Prescription Drug Payment Review Commission, 1988 (Box 235, Folder 6)
    - Primarius, 1987 (Box 235, Folder 7)
    - Professional Liability Insurance, 1993 (Box 235, Folder 8)
    - Professional Society Insurance Service, 1987-1992 (Box 235, Folder 9)
    - Public Health Service Advisory Commission on Childhood Vaccines, 1988 (Box 235, Folder 10)
    - Purdue-Frederick, 1984-1993 (Box 235, Folder 11)
    - Puritan Corporation Grants, Correspondence, 1959 (Box 446, Folder 41)
    - Quidel, 1988 (Box 235, Folder 12)
    - Radionics Medical, 1985 (Box 235, Folder 13)
    - Ralston Purina, 1961 (Box 446, Folder 42)
    - Regional, State and Local Allergy, Asthma and Immunology Societies
      - AAAAI Tool Kit: Resources for Growing Your RSLAAI Society, 2005 (Box 670, Folder 7)
      - Allergy and Asthma Proceedings, 2002 November/December-2004 September/October (Box 537, Folder 57-66)
      - Business Meeting, Reports, 2000, 2002 (Box 446, Folder 44)
      - Officer Roster, 1996-1998 (Box 520, Folder 35)
      - Physicians and Public Services Council, Notes, 1991-1995 (Box 675, Folder 10)
    - Regional, State, and Local Allergy Societies
      - Minutes and Notes
        - 1993 (Box 461, Folder 5)
        - 1995-1997 (Box 446, Folder 45-46)
        - 1997 (Box 680, Folder 1-2)
        - 1998 (Box 670, Folder 8-9)
        - 1999-2001 (Box 680, Folder 3-6)
        - 2001-2004 (Box 681, Folder 1-6)
      - Strategic Roundtable, 2000 (Box 429, Folder 2)
    - Related Organizations
      - 1983 (Box 170, Folder 1)
      - Council, 1987-1995 (Box 170, Folder 2)
      - Goals and Objectives, 1981-1986 (Box 261, Folder 7)
      - Information, 1989 (Box 170, Folder 3-5)
    - Research America, 1994-1995 (Box 235, Folder 14)
    - Residency Review Committee for Allergy and Immunology, 1986 (Box 235, Folder 15)
    - Rhone-Poulenc Rorer, 1991-1995 (Box 235, Folder 16)
    - Riker Laboratories, 1985-1989 (Box 235, Folder 17)
    - A.H. Robbins Company, 1985 (Box 235, Folder 18)
    - Roche Laboratories, 1986 (Box 235, Folder 19)
    - Roerig, 1988 (Box 235, Folder 20)
    - Ross Laboratories, 1976-1988 (Box 236, Folder 1)
    - Royal College of Physicians, 1992 (Box 236, Folder 2)
    - Royal Society of Medicine, 1987-1993 (Box 236, Folder 3)
    - Sandoz Pharmaceuticals, 1988-1994 (Box 236, Folder 4)
    - Saving Lives Coalition Planning Committee, 1992 (Box 236, Folder 5)
    - SchenLabs Pharmaceuticals, 1959 (Box 446, Folder 43)
    - Schering Corporation
      - 1951-1969 (Box 446, Folder 47)
      - 1977-1995 (Box 236, Folder 6-7)
    - Searle Laboratories, 1983-1994 (Box 236, Folder 8)
    - Sheldon Memorial Lectureship, 1968-1983 (Box 236, Folder 9)
    - Smith, Kline and French Laboratories, 1986 (Box 236, Folder 10)
    - Sociedad Latinoamericana de Alergia e Immunologia, 1987 (Box 236, Folder 11)
    - Society for Clinical Immunology, 1986 (Box 236, Folder 12)
    - Society for the Advancement of Women's Health Research, 1993 (Box 236, Folder 13)
    - Society of Behavioral Medicine, 1982-1986 (Box 236, Folder 14)
    - Syntex Laboratories, 1984-1987 (Box 236, Folder 15)
    - Thermologica, 1995 (Box 236, Folder 16)
    - 3M Diagnostic Systems, 1985-1992 (Box 236, Folder 17)
    - Transpacific Allergy and Immunology Society, 1997, 2000, undated (Box 377, Folder 11)
    - Travenol Laboratories, 1986 (Box 236, Folder 18)
    - UCB Institute of Allergy, 1987-1990 (Box 236, Folder 19)
    - United States Pharmacopeial Convention
      - 1986-1988 (Box 236, Folder 20)
      - 1989-1996 (Box 237, Folder 1-5)
    - University of Wisconsin Medical School,Dialogues in Redefining Allergy, 1997-1998 (Box 492, Folder 8)
    - Upjohn Company, 1985 (Box 237, Folder 6)
    - Ventrex Laboratories, 1986-1990 (Box 237, Folder 7)
    - Veteran's Administration Medical Care and Health Research, 1988 (Box 237, Folder 8)
    - Washington State Society of Allergy, Asthma and Immunology, 1995 (Box 543, Folder 52)
    - Winthrop-Breon Laboratories, 1983-1987 (Box 237, Folder 9)
    - Wisconsin Allergy Society, 1988-1990 (Box 237, Folder 10)
    - Wisconsin Nurses Association, 1995 (Box 237, Folder 11)
    - World Allergy Organization, Meeting Announcement, 2002 (Box 472, Folder 4)
    - World Health Organization, 1989-1992 (Box 237, Folder 12)
    - Wyeth, 1988 (Box 237, Folder 13)
    - Xenejenex, 1991 (Box 237, Folder 14)
    - Zeneca, 1995 (Box 543, Folder 26)
  - 6. Member Files, 1950s-2000s
    This series was returned to the AAAAI in October 2009.
  - 7. Audio-Visual Materials, 1937-2015
    Included in this series are photographs, including annual meeting, past president and Board of Directors photographs. Also included are videocassettes of annual meetings, as well as productions sponsored by the AAAI. Most of the CDs, DVDs, and beta tapes are audio only. Audio cassettes contain continuing education courses sponsored by the AAAI and the AAAAI, as well as recordings of paper presentations at annual meetings. Most audio cassettes are recording of sessions presented at annual meetings. Boxes 728 and 730 include a paper index that describes the contents of the audio cassettes from boxes 728 and 730.
    Audio cassettes are housed in boxes 391-403, 497, 523, 528-531, 542, and 728-733. Videocassettes are housed in boxes 408-414 and 497. Photographs are housed in boxes 330-334, 430, and 441.
    - 7A. Videocassettes and Film, 1982-2004, undated
      - Annual Meetings
        - 1982
          - Report on Allergy, Videocassette (U-matic) (Box 410)
        - 1984
          - Highlights, Videocassette (VHS) (Box 408)
        - 1988
          - Allergy Seminar, 10 videocassettes (U-matic) (Box 413-414)
          - Annual Meeting, Videocassette (VHS) (Box 408)
          - Annual Meeting, 9 Videocassettes (U-matic) (Box 413)
          - Daily Highlights, Days 1-4, 2 videocassettes (VHS) (Box 408)
          - Exhibit Hall Footage, Videocassette (VHS) (Box 408)
        - 1989
          - Annual Meeting, 5 videocassettes (VHS) (Box 409)
          - Interviews, 6 videocassettes (U-matic) (Box 411)
          - Interviews, 6 videocassettes (U-matic) (Box 414)
          - Pre-production, Videocassette (U-matic) (Box 413)
        - 1991
          - Annual Meeting, Videocassette (VHS) (Box 408)
        - 1992
          - Annual Meeting, Videocassette (VHS) (Box 408)
        - 1994
          - Poster Sessions, Videocassette (VHS) (Box 408)
        - 1995
          - Annual Meeting, Videocassette (Beta) (Box 408)
          - Collaborative Investigator's Symposium, 2 videocassettes (VHS) (Box 409)
          - Global Initiatives for Asthma, 2 videocassettes (VHS) (Box 410)
          - Postgraduate Plenary Session, 2 videocassettes (VHS) (Box 409)
          - Presidential Plenary Symposium, 2 videocassettes (VHS) (Box 410)
        - 1996
          - Asthma's Consultant's Course, 2 videocassettes (VHS) (Box 410)
          - European Academy of Allergy and Clinical Immunology/AACI/AAAAI Joint Symposium, 2 videocassettes (VHS) (Box 410)
          - Postgraduate Education Plenary Program: Cellular Programs in the Immune System, 2 videocassettes (VHS) (Box 410)
          - Postgraduate Education Plenary Program: Gene Expression & Allergic Diseases, 2 videocassettes (VHS) (Box 410)
        - 1997
          - Business Meeting, 1 videocassette (VHS) (Box 408)
          - News 3 This Morning, KYW-TV (CBS) Philadelphia, 1 videocassette (VHS) (Box 408)
        - 1999
          - Business Meeting, Videocassette (VHS) (Box 408)
          - Newsline, Orlando, 4 videocassettes (VHS) (Box 409)
        - 2000
          - Newsline, San Diego, 4 videocassettes (VHS) (Box 409)
        - 2001
          - Newsline, New Orleans, 4 videocassettes (VHS) (Box 409)
        - 2002
          - Newsline, New York, 4 videocassettes (VHS)
        - 2004
          - Business Meeting, Videocassette (VHS) (Box 408)
      - Continuing Education
        - Allergic Rhinitis... Nothing to Sneeze at, 1986, Videocassette (VHS) (Box 410)
        - Allergic Rhino-Sinusitis, 2001, Videocassette (VHS) (Box 408)
        - Allergy, 1983, 8 videocassettes (U-matic) (Box 411)
        - Allergy Essentials: Allergic Rhino Conjunctivitis, Anaphylaxis, Asthma, Urticaria Angiodema, undated, 4 videocassettes (VHS) (Box 408)
        - Allergy Film, undated, Film reel (16 mm) (Film 1)
        - Allergy Topics '99, 1999, Videocassette (VHS) (Box 408)
        - Asthma Management, 1997, Videocassette (VHS) (Box 410)
        - Capitalizing on Capitation: The Allergist and Managed Care, 1996, Videocassette (VHS) (Box 408)
        - Environment, Allergies & You, 1989, Videocassette (VHS) (Box 408)
        - Environment & Occupational Disorders Mini-symposium: Indoor Allergens Cloning to Cleaning, undated, 2 videocassettes (VHS) (Box 409)
        - Food Allergy, 2001, Videocassette (VHS) (Box 408)
        - Immunopathogens of the HIV disease, undated, Videocassette (VHS) (Box 409)
        - Immunotherapy: Old Fashioned or Futuristic, 1986, Videocassette (VHS) (Box 410)
        - Modified Skin Prick Test, undated, Videocassette (VHS) (Box 408)
        - New Developments in Clinical Immunology, undated, Videocassette (VHS) (Box 409)
        - Occupational Related Diseases, undated, Videocassette (VHS) (Box 409)
        - Using the Metered Dose Inhaler, 1991, Videocassette (VHS) (Box 410)
      - Miscellaneous
        - Communications, Public Relations and News Footage, 1994, Videocassette (VHS) (Box 408)
        - Executive Director Program, undated, 42 videocassettes (VHS) (Box 412)
        - I'm Wonderful & Have Asthma, 1988, Videocassette (VHS) (Box 408)
        - Making the News, 1999, Videocassette (VHS) (Box 408)
        - Membership Meeting, undated, Videocassette (VHS) (Box 408)
        - Public Information Program, 1989, Videocassette (VHS) (Box 408)
        - Public Service Announcements, 1988, Videocassette (VHS) (Box 408)
        - Rachelefsky, Gary, Today Show Interview, 1991, Videocassette (VHS) (Box 408)
        - Teleconference, 1993, 2 videocassettes (VHS) (Box 408)
        - Visit to the Allergy Doctor, 1985, Videocassette (VHS) (Box 408)